League of Women Voters of Rensselaer County Records apap103
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Publications, 1942-2006; Undated; 2; 1.20 cubic ft.
  - Day Care: Community Challenge and Responsibility, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 34)
  - Report on Housing in Rensselaer County, 1970 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 35)
  - Bulletin, 1970 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 36)
  - Bulletin, 1971 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 37)
  - Bulletin, 1972 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 38)
  - Bulletin, 1973 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 39)
  - Bulletin, 1974 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 40)
  - Bulletin, 1975 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 41)
  - Bulletin, 1976 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 42)
  - Bulletin, 1977 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 43)
  - Local Government, 1977 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 44)
  - Bulletin, 1978 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 45)
  - Bulletin, 1979 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 46)
  - Bulletin, 1980 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 47)
  - Bulletin, 1981 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 48)
  - Bulletin, 1982 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 49)
  - Bulletin, 1983 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 50)
  - "A Great Idea through the Years: 1920 to Present", 1984 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 51)
  - Bulletin, 1984 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 52)
  - Bulletin, 1985 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 53)
  - Bulletin, 1986 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 54)
  - The Voter, 1986-1988 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 55)
  - Bulletin, 1987 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 56)
  - Easy-to-READ Voter Registration Facts Pamphlets, 1988 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 57)
  - In League: League of Women Voters of the United States, 1989 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 58)
  - The Voter, 1989-1991 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 59)
  - Bulletin, 1990 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 60)
  - The Voter, 1992-1995 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 61)
  - A Citizen's Guide to Local Governments in Rensselaer County, 1993-1995 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 62)
  - "Action in Albany", 1994-1997 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 63)
  - "Getting into the Issues: Your Guide to the 1996 Elections" (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 64)
  - The Voter, 1996-1999 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 1)
  - The National Voter, 1997 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 2)
  - Candidates for Office in Rensselaer County, 1997 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 3)
  - Election 1997 Brochures (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 4)
  - Voting in General, 1997-1998 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 5)
  - The Voter, 2000-2003 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 6)
  - The Voter, 2004-2006 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 7)
  - "A Report to the Nation on the Activities of the League of Women Voters of the United States", Undated (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 8)
- Rensselaer County Government, ca. 1943-2002; Undated; 3; 0.90 cubic ft.
  Series 3, Rensselaer County Government, provides a chronological record of the League's activities concerning the county government from 1952 to 1982. Some of the subject areas include apportionment, the charter, economic development, fair campaign practices and lobbying. The series contains materials on Know Your Rensselaer County, an effort by the LWVRC to bring awareness to Rensselaer County residents about the county government and electoral process within the county. The LWVRC has been involved in this effort since the 1940s, surveying and evaluating the status of the county government and its projects at any given time. The League was especially interested in public health (tuberculosis in particular), children's services, and the county's welfare administration in the 1940s. However, its interests also included jury selection, election participation, population, economy and local history. In the 1960s, the LWVRC began drafting Know Your Rensselaer County, which provided a portrait of the county's various departments, elected offices, and public projects. In 1972, county voters passed a charter-form of government. As a result, the League would become a sort of "watchdog" group for the implementation and execution of the goals of the charter, as will be seen in Series 6. By 1992, the LWVRC published the Rensselaer County Government Workbook as part of its review of the charter. It also expressed the League's position, supporting the County Charter. The purpose of the workbook was to "share information about the County Charter with students and teachers of High School Participation in Government classes as part of the Bicentennial Commission's Education Program."
  - Know Your Rensselaer County, ca. 1943 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 1)
  - Rensselaer County Government, 1952 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 2)
  - Rensselaer County Government, 1953 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 3)
  - Rensselaer County Government, 1954 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 4)
  - Economic Characteristics of Rensselaer County, ca. 1955 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 5)
  - Rensselaer County Government, 1955 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 6)
  - Rensselaer County Government, 1956 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 7)
  - Rensselaer County Government, 1958 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 8)
  - Rensselaer County Government, 1961 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 9)
  - Know Your Rensselaer County Draft on Government, Services, and History, 1965 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 10-11)
  - Know Your Rensselaer County Draft on Education Sections and Private Agencies, 1965 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 12)
  - Know Your Rensselaer County, 1965 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 13)
  - Rensselaer County Government, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 14)
  - Rensselaer County Government, 1968 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 15)
  - Commission on Economic Opportunity, 1968 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 16)
  - Know Your Rensselaer County, 1968 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 17)
  - Rensselaer County Government, Court Ruled Apportionment, 1968 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 18)
  - Rensselaer County Government, 1969 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 19)
  - Charter Study, 1970 (Oversized 2, Folder 1)
  - Rensselaer County Government, Budget, 1970 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 20)
  - Rensselaer County Government, Charter Study, 1970 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 21)
  - Local Governments in Rensselaer County: Towns, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 22)
  - Chart Showing the Proposed Form of Government, 1971 (Oversized 2, Folder 2)
  - League of Women Voters Study of the County Charter, 1971 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 23)
  - Rensselaer County Government, Voters Services, 1971 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 24)
  - Rensselaer County Government, 1971 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 25)
  - Rensselaer County Planning and the League of Women Voters' Position, 1971 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 26)
  - Know Your Rensselaer County, ca. 1972 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 27)
  - Rensselaer County Government, Voters Services, 1972 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 28)
  - Rensselaer County Government, Action Supporting County Charter, 1972 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 29)
  - Rensselaer County Government, 1973 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 30)
  - Rensselaer County Government, 1975 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 31)
  - Rensselaer County Government, 1976 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 32)
  - Flyer for the Rensselaer County Charter Referendum, 1976 (Oversized 1, Folder 2)
  - Know Your Rensselaer County, 1977 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 33)
  - Rensselaer County Government, 1978 (Box 1 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 34)
  - Rensselaer County Government, 1980 (Box 2 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 1)
  - Rensselaer County Government, 1982 (Box 2 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 2)
  - Rensselaer County Commission on Economic Development, 1968-1972 (Box 2 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 3)
  - Rensselaer County Legislature, League of Women Voters Study of Reapportionment, 1981 (Box 2 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 4)
  - Rensselaer County Legislature, League of Women Voters Position on Reapportionment and Lobbying, 1982 (Box 2 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 5)
  - Family Court, 1989 (Box 2 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 6)
  - Rensselaer County Government, History and Mary Stierer's Script for a Skit at a League of Women Voters Membership Meeting, ca. 1991 (Box 2 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 7)
  - Rensselaer County Government Workbook, 1991 (Box 2 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 8)
  - Rensselaer County Government Workbook, 1991-1993 (Box 2 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 9-10)
  - Know Your Rensselaer County, Rensselaer County Government Workbook, 1991-1993 (Oversized 1, Folder 4)
  - Redistricting Rensselaer County Legislature, 1991-1994 (Box 2 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 11)
  - County Charter Study, 1991-1995; Undated (Box 2 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 12)
  - Rensselaer County Budget, 1993 (Box 2 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 13)
  - Single Member Districts, 1993 (Box 2 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 14)
  - Court Mandated Study, 1993 (Box 2 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 15)
  - Statements and Correspondence, 1993-2002 (Box 2 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 16)
  - Local Government Consolidation Flyer, 1994 (Box 2 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 17)
  - Rensselaer County Government Workbook, 1994; 1996-1997 (Box 2 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 18)
  - Rensselaer County Government Quiz, 1995 (Box 2 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 19)
  - Registration and Voting in Rensselaer County, 1998 (Box 2 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 20)
  - Redistricting the Rensselaer County Legislature, 2001 (Box 2 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 21)
  - Lobbying Report Forms, 2002 (Box 2 (3-Rensselaer County Government), Folder 22)
- Local Program Studies, 1946-2006; Undated; 4; 1.28 cubic ft.
  Series 4, Local Program Studies, includes documentation about the various projects and programs that the LWVRC has taken on. Again focusing on elections and financing, particularly in the schools, the LWVRC provided information to the citizens of the county. Aside from public school related projects, the LWVRC took on apportionment, city planning, land use, criminal justice court reform, human resources development, environment, ERA, health care, housing, international relations, arms control, New York State politics, revenue sharing and reproductive rights.
  - Schools, 1946 (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 1)
  - League of Women Voters School Elections, 1946-1955 (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 2)
  - School Financing, 1953 (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 3)
  - School Financing, 1954 (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 4)
  - International Relations, Bricker Amendment, 1954 (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 5)
  - Criminal Justice Court Reform, 1954-1975 (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 6)
  - Know Your Schools, City of Troy, 1955 (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 7)
  - Schools, 1955 (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 8)
  - Know Your Schools, 1956 (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 9)
  - School Financing, 1956 (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 10)
  - Water Resources Study, 1956-1957; 1964-1965 (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 11)
  - School Financing, 1957 (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 12)
  - Individual Liberties, Federal Loyalty Security Program, 1957 (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 13)
  - School Financing, 1958 (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 14)
  - School Financing, 1959 (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 15)
  - City Planning, Troy Urban Renewal, 1960-1964 (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 16)
  - Troy School Budget, 1961 (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 17)
  - Water Pollution Study, 1966-1970 (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 18)
  - Water Resources, 1964-1965 (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 19)
  - Parks and Recreation in Rensselaer County, 1964-1971 (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 20)
  - Apportionment, 1964-1968; Undated (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 21)
  - National League of Women Voters, Development of Human Resources, Education and Employment, 1965-1967 (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 22)
  - International Relations, Trade, 1965-1970 (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 23)
  - Hudson River Basin Study, 1966 (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 24)
  - League of Women Voters of the United States, School Elections, 1966-1970 (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 25)
  - New York State Constitution, 1966-1970 (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 26)
  - OEO/CEO Study/Support, 1966-1972 (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 27)
  - School Lunches in Troy Schools, 1967; 1971-1973 (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 28)
  - Development of Human Resources, Education and Employment Local Study, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 29)
  - Development of Human Resources, Education and Employment, 1967-1968 (Oversized 1, Folder 7)
  - Development of Human Resources, Local Study, Education and Up the Ladder Publication, 1968-1969 (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 1)
  - Electoral College Study, 1968-1970 (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 2)
  - International Relations, China, 1968-1970 (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 3)
  - Solid Waste Management, 1968-1984 (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 4)
  - Development of Human Resources, Housing in Rensselaer County, 1968-1970 (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 5)
  - Housing, 1969 (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 6)
  - International Relations, Foreign Economic Policy, 1969 (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 7)
  - Development of Human Resources, Day Care Council, 1969 (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 8)
  - Development of Human Resources, Education, 1969 (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 9)
  - International Relations, Foreign Policy, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 10)
  - School Financing, 1970 (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 11)
  - Development of Human Resources, Up the Ladder Update, 1970 (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 12)
  - Land Use County Planning Study, 1970-1971 (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 13)
  - Development of Human Resources, Alternatives to Welfare, 1970-1971 (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 14)
  - League of Women Voters Election Law Study, 1970-1972 (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 15)
  - Housing, Urban Renewal, 1970-1977 (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 16)
  - Home Rule, Washington DC, 1971 (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 17)
  - Know Your Schools, 1971 (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 18)
  - Environmental Quality, Clear Air, 1971 (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 19)
  - League of Women Voters of the United States, School Elections, 1971 (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 20)
  - Government, Study of Congress, 1971-1972; Undated (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 21)
  - School Lunch, Troy, 1971-1973 (Oversized 1, Folder 5)
  - School Elections, 1972 (Oversized 1, Folder 6)
  - Voters Service, School Elections, 1972 (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 22)
  - ILO, Regional Planning, 1972 (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 23)
  - Schools, 1972 (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 24)
  - ILO, Regional Planning, 1972 (Oversized 1, Folder 9)
  - School Financing, 1972-1973 (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 25)
  - Development of Human Resources, Welfare Reform, 1972-1977 (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 26)
  - Revenue Sharing, 1973-1974 (Oversized 2, Folder 3)
  - Revenue Sharing, 1973-1974 (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 27)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1973-1979 (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 28)
  - Property Tax, 1974-1980; 1983; Undated (Box 2 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 29)
  - Property Tax, 1974-1980; 1983; Undated (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 1)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, New York State Constitutional Amendment, 1975 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 2)
  - Health Care in Rensselaer County, 1973-1974 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 3)
  - League of Women Voters of the United States, School Elections, 1973-1976 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 4)
  - School Financing, 1974-1975 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 5)
  - Know Your Schools, 1975 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 6)
  - New York State Legislature Study, 1975-1976 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 7)
  - School Financing, 1976 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 8)
  - International Relations, United Nations Study, 1976-1977 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 9)
  - Energy, 1977 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 10)
  - Energy, 1977 (Oversized 1, Folder 8)
  - State Government Initiative and Referendum, 1977-1979 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 11)
  - School Financing, 1977 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 12)
  - Coastal Management I.L.O. Project, 1977 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 13)
  - Rensselaer County Open Meeting Law Observer Corps, 1978-1979 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 14)
  - New York State Election Law, 1978-1983 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 15)
  - Human Resources Update, including Legal Services, 1980-1981 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 16)
  - School Financing, 1981 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 17)
  - School Financing, 1982 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 18)
  - New Federalism, 1982 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 19)
  - Reproduction Rights, 1982 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 20)
  - Women and the Law, 1982 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 21)
  - National Security, Arms Control, 1983-1986 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 22)
  - Solid Waste Management, 1985-1987 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 23)
  - Local Study, Single Member Legislature Districts in Rensselaer County, 1990 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, General, 1992 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 25)
  - Proposed Ref-Fuel Incinerator on Green Island, 1995 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 26)
  - Financing Education Consensus, 1997 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 27)
  - Balancing Justice in New York State, 2000-2001 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 28)
  - Balancing Justice in New York State, 2003 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 29)
  - Voting Machines, 2006 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 30)
  - Financing Education and Charter School Consensus, 2006 (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 31)
  - Land Use, Undated (Box 3 (4-Local Program Studies), Folder 32)
- Troy City Government, 1939-2004; Undated; 5; 0.85 cubic ft.
  Series 5, Troy Government, is similar to Series 3 in that the documents provide a chronological account of the LWVRC's involvement in the affairs of Troy's government. The series contains material about the Troy City Charter as the LWVRC has been involved in the oversight and development of Troy's charter since the 1950s. In more recent times, the League has been involved in charter campaigns and revisions, examining the role of the mayor and developing questionnaires about how to improve the city's charter.
  - Troy Government, 1939 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 1)
  - Troy Government, 1949 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 2)
  - Troy Government, 1953 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 3)
  - Troy Government, 1955 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 4)
  - Troy Government, 1956 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 5)
  - City Charter, 1956 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 6)
  - Troy Government, 1957 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 7)
  - Troy Government, 1958 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 8)
  - Troy Government, 1959 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 9)
  - City Charter, 1959 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 10)
  - City Charter, ca. 1960 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 11)
  - Troy Government, 1960 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 12)
  - Troy Government, 1961 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 13)
  - Troy Government, 1962 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 14)
  - Troy Government, 1963 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 15)
  - Troy Government, 1964 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 16)
  - Map of Troy's Seven City Council Districts, 1964 (Oversized 1, Folder 10)
  - Troy Government, 1965 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 17)
  - Troy Government, 1966 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 18)
  - Troy Government, 1967 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 19)
  - Troy Government, 1968 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 20)
  - Troy Government, 1969 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 21)
  - Petition to the City Council, 1969 (Oversized 1, Folder 11)
  - City Charter Questionnaire, 1970 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 22)
  - Troy Government, 1970 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 23)
  - City Charter, 1971 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 24)
  - Troy Government, 1972 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 25)
  - Troy Government, 1973 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 26)
  - Troy Government, 1974 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 27)
  - City Charter, 1975 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 28)
  - Troy Government, 1976 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 29)
  - City Charter, 1976 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 30)
  - City Charter, Questionnaire, 1976 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 31)
  - City Charter, Guide for League of Women Voters' Questionnaire, 1976 (Box 1 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 32)
  - Troy Government, includes Personnel Management/Affirmative Action Study, 1977 (Box 2 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 1)
  - Troy Government, 1978 (Box 2 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 2)
  - Troy Government, 1979 (Box 2 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 3)
  - City Charter, Revision Commission, 1979-1980 (Box 2 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 4)
  - City Charter, Media, 1980 (Box 2 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 5)
  - City Charter, Study, 1980 (Box 2 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 6)
  - City Charter, Study on Transparencies, 1980 (Box 2 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 7)
  - Troy Government, 1980 (Box 2 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 8)
  - City Charter, 1980-1982 (Box 2 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 9)
  - Troy Government, 1981 (Box 2 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 10)
  - Troy Government, 1982 (Box 2 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 11)
  - Troy Government, 1984 (Box 2 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 12)
  - Statement to the City of Troy Planning Board on behalf of Unity House, 1989-1990 (Box 2 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 13)
  - City Charter, 1992 (Box 2 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 14)
  - City Charter, Role of the Mayor, 1992-1993 (Box 2 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 15)
  - City Charter Study, 1992-1993 (Box 2 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 16)
  - City Charter Revision, 1993 (Box 2 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 17)
  - League of Women Voters Against a Strong Mayor Referendum, 1994 (Box 2 (5-Troy City Government), Folder 18)